Hamzah Imanul Haq

Geologist - GIS - Programmer



My Contact

- M hamzahhaqimanul@gmail.com
- +6281245314790
- Bangka raya, South Jakarta
- hamzahimanulhaq.github.io

Software Skill

- Arcgis Pro, Arcmap, Global mapper, Qgis, AutoCAD
- Surpac, Micromine
- · Logchief, DataShead
- Adobe Illustrator, Photoshop, Premier Pro
- Ms. Office

Programming language

- · HTML, PHP, CSS
- JavaScipt, Python, C++
- SQL, Macros
- · Arcade, VB script

Education Background

- Bandung Institute of Technology Geology Engineering
 Aug 2014 - Oct 2018
- Hactive 8
 Fullstack WEB Development
 2021

Achievements

2022 Executed a strategic plan for a project (mining concessions) which saves company's finance by 42 billion IDR

2021 Discovered new gold prospect (assay up to 3 ppm) during a Gold-Copper exploration program in Kalimantan

About Me

A dedicated and enthusiastic Exploration Geology, Mining, and GIS analyst with over 3 years of experience as a field geologist keen in programming software in a self-taught manner. Loves creative things such as design, photography and videography.

Professional Experience

Peakglobal Resources Consulting | GIS - Database Geologist 2021 - Present

Key responsibilities:

- Creates and designs a mapping application in the form of interactive WebGIS dashboard by utilizing multiple use of GIS softwares (i.e ArcGIS, QGIS, GlobalMapper) for ease of other departments and users' accessibility within the company
- Implements knowledge on SQL and PHP to construct a database used to store technical drilling information
- Prepares detailed research presentation and evaluation work reports encompassing the on-going mapping projects in Kalimantan

Bapenda DKI Jakarta | Field Manager 2020 – 2021

Key responsibilities:

- Assigning territories, schedules, and appropriate supplies and equipment to staff members
- Training and motivating field workers
- Helping employees to improve and tracking employee progress
- Responding to all on-call tasks and supporting the Field

PT Amman Mineral | Regional Exploration Geologist 2018 – 2020

Elang Exploration Project - Ladam Prospect (Epithermal Deposit), Lampui Prospect (Epithermal-Porphyry Deposit), and Sepekat Prospect (Porphyry Deposit).

Key responsibilities:

- · Planning site exploration programmes
- Surveying and mapping sites
- Wellsite and Supervision of RIG in site
- Collecting, QAQC and preparing for analysis samples
- · Preparing and presenting reports.

References

Hery Sulistiyo

Manager Exploration PT Amman Mineral +6281340218666

Lambok Hutasoit

Professor Geology Department Bandung Institute of Technology +62811213420